//Questions
export const quizQuestions = [
    {
      question:
        "What is one of the main objectives of sustainable tourism?",
      answers: [
        "Maximize short-term profits",
        "Minimize environmental and social impact",
        "Promote luxury tourist destinations only",
        "Increase mass tourism",
      ],
      correct_answer: "Minimize environmental and social impact",
    },
    {
      question:
        "What does the acronym 'CO2' mean in the context of sustainable tourism?",
      answers: [
        "City, Hospitality, 2nd World",
        "2-hour Operational Change",
        "Carbon Dioxide",
        "Trade of Organic Items 2",
      ],
      correct_answer: "Carbon Dioxide",
    },
    {
      question: "What are the three main dimensions of sustainable tourism?",
      answers: [
        "Economic, Political, Technological",
        "Environmental, Social, Economic",
        "Cultural, Historical, Artistic",
        "Physical, Chemical, Biological",
      ],
      correct_answer: "Environmental, Social, Economic",
    },
    {
      question: "What does 'ecotourism' mean?",
      answers: [
        "Tourism in space",
        "Responsible and ecological tourism",
        "Tourism within eco-friendly cities",
        "Tourism in industrial areas",
      ],
      correct_answer: "Responsible and ecological tourism",
    },
    {
      question: "Which tourism activities are considered sustainable?",
      answers: [
        "Hiking, wildlife observation, cycling tourism",
        "Luxury cruises, hunting safaris, private flights",
        "Theme parks, nightclub tours, excessive shopping",
        "All of the above activities",
      ],
      correct_answer:
        "Hiking, wildlife observation, cycling tourism",
    },
    {
      question: "What does sustainable cultural tourism promote?",
      answers: [
        "Destruction of cultural sites",
        "Preservation of culture and heritage",
        "Sale of non-authentic souvenirs",
        "Illegal trade of art objects",
      ],
      correct_answer: "Preservation of culture and heritage",
    },
    {
      question:
        "What does 'carbon offsetting' represent in sustainable tourism?",
      answers: [
        "An ecological mode of transportation",
        "A method to offset carbon emissions",
        "A training program for tourism operators",
        "A tax for tourists",
      ],
      correct_answer: "A method to offset carbon emissions",
    },
    {
      question: "What is one of the negative impacts of mass tourism?",
      answers: [
        "Improvement of local infrastructure",
        "Preservation of natural resources",
        "Overcrowding, pollution, and resource overexploitation",
        "Increased cultural diversity",
      ],
      correct_answer:
        "Overcrowding, pollution, and resource overexploitation",
    },
    {
      question: "What is one of the key principles of sustainable tourism?",
      answers: [
        "Maximize natural resource consumption",
        "Promote the expansion of international hotel chains",
        "Respect the environment and local cultures",
        "Offer inexpensive tourist packages",
      ],
      correct_answer: "Respect the environment and local cultures",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the goal of responsible tourism?",
      answers: [
        "Maximize natural resource consumption",
        "Promote Western culture",
        "Improve the well-being of local communities and environmental conservation",
        "Increase waste production",
      ],
      correct_answer:
        "Improve the well-being of local communities and environmental conservation",
    },
  ];
  